<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Both Are True</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Both Are True</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.150.1</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>positioning</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/positioning/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/positioning/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m reading this book - a classic in the marketing world, apparently, called Positioning. Here&amp;rsquo;s a lil bit from the intro:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;[!from the book]
Positioning has changed the way the advertising game is being played today.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We’re the third largest-selling coffee in America,” say the Sanka radio commercials.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The third largest? Whatever happened to those good old advertising words like “first” and “best” and “finest”?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, the good old advertising days are gone forever and so are the words. Today you find comparatives, not superlatives.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>true commitment to the bit</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/true-commitment-to-the-bit/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/true-commitment-to-the-bit/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;![Pasted image 20251017213150.png](/images/Pasted image 20251017213150.png)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Soooo this actor and writer Richard Ayoade wrote a book called The Unfinished Harauld Hughes which is about a writer of books and screenplays and other things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And as part of writing that book, Ayoade also wrote and published actual books by his fictional character Harauld Hughes!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;rsquo;s Wallace Shawn explaining what Ayoade did:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;_many writers have invented characters who are writers—but do you know any other writer who has not only invented a character who is a writer but who has then gone on to actually write and publish that imaginary writer’s complete works? Richard Ayoade has done that, and if you take out your Kindle and look up Harauld Hughes, Faber will be glad to send you Hughes’s collected plays, poems, prose pieces, and screenplays, all in fact written by Richard Ayoade.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are You Inside the Work or Outside the Work?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/are-you-inside-the-work-or-outside-the-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/are-you-inside-the-work-or-outside-the-work/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Are you inside the work or outside the work?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s basically another way of talking about status and mastery, but I think it&amp;rsquo;s a nice shortcut. Where are you? Are you in it—actually doing the thing—or are you outside, staring at the finished product, obsessing over how other people are going to receive it?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My new theory is this: the only real home is inside. That&amp;rsquo;s the only place you can actually live.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inspirations</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/inspirations/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/inspirations/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As I venture forth into this new wilderness, I find myself returning again and again to influences and inspirations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Specifically, I want to write them down, for myself, and share them, for y&amp;rsquo;all. It&amp;rsquo;s way too easy to forget about them in the maelstrom of the day, the hubbub of the night.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, in no particular order, here are some people whose work inspires me and to whom I look when thinking about this next chapter:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Links</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/links/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/links/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Inspired by &lt;a href=&#34;https://matklad.github.io/2025/08/23/links.html&#34;&gt;this&lt;/a&gt; I am starting a links page.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What will I put here is to be determined of course.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Update (09-20-25):&lt;/strong&gt;
I need multiple link pages. One is probably best for self-promo and BAT-promo.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Site I Like: Ryan Hemsworth (Musician)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/site-i-like-ryan-hemsworth/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/site-i-like-ryan-hemsworth/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ryanhemsworth.com/&#34;&gt;https://www.ryanhemsworth.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I mean come on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also this &amp;lsquo;submit a drawing thing&amp;rsquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;(Note: Original had images that couldn&amp;rsquo;t be transferred - check out the site itself!)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;rsquo;s the one I did:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;(Drawing reference in original)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BATCAVE Promo</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/batcave-promo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/batcave-promo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Check out this piece on rituals and members clubs:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://shindy.substack.com/p/rituals-members-clubs&#34;&gt;https://shindy.substack.com/p/rituals-members-clubs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blend vs Mix</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/blend-vs-mix/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/blend-vs-mix/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I just want to give a big shout out to the word &amp;lsquo;blend.&amp;rsquo; Coffee is a blend. I just made a blend when i took beans from two different bags and tossed it all into my grinder. That is a blend!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The word blend is powerful. It is a marketing word.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Imagine if you were paying for a &amp;lsquo;coffee mix&amp;rsquo; - I would not pay top dollar for that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Blend though, now blend sounds good.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t Spoil Your Effort by Seeking for Shelter</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/dont-spoil-your-effort-by-seeking-shelter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/dont-spoil-your-effort-by-seeking-shelter/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Love this line so much from &amp;ldquo;not always so&amp;rdquo; by Shunryu Suzuki.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And the line he says a bit earlier: &amp;ldquo;if you go to the rest room, there is a chance for enlightenment.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But when you go to the restroom and seek shelter inside your phone, there is no chance for enlightenment. Of course there is, still, because the person who is looking in their phone is also enlightened but he does not know it to be so.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Idea: A Website for BAT Workshops</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/idea-website-for-bat-workshops/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/idea-website-for-bat-workshops/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;spec:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ADD&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ideas:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;have a chat like &lt;a href=&#34;https://iframe.chat/&#34;&gt;this&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People Who Seem Awesome That I&#39;d Love to Work With</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/people-who-seem-awesome/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/people-who-seem-awesome/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://sundogcowboy.com/&#34;&gt;https://sundogcowboy.com/&lt;/a&gt; - Jess Hererra who designed Cody Cook-Parrott&amp;rsquo;s website which seems awesome&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Internet Is a Temper Trap Hell Hole</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-internet-is-a-temper-trap-hell-hole/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-internet-is-a-temper-trap-hell-hole/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I wrote this at Sept 28 at 4:04am&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;rsquo;t know how else to put it. Today, this morning (Sept 28), just now, at 4:04am, I cut my journaling into my little notebook with my little pencil short - I cut it short so I could get on and write into my big computer with my big keyboard the big idea I had about the word blend.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But when I got onto the computer, this vegas strip with its bright lights and flashing distractions all hand crafted and premium made for me truly, exactly as I left it last night, I forgot all about blend.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Do I Define Mastery for Myself?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-do-i-define-mastery-for-myself/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-do-i-define-mastery-for-myself/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;When thinking about mastery, for myself, there seem to be two frames:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How do I define what it means to strive for learning, for mastery?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How well am I following that rubric / framework for any given essay?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think I need to figure out #1 first, or at least have some sense of it, in order to give it a whirl. But I also need to not be too prescriptive. Who knows what&amp;rsquo;ll happen when I write.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forgiveness (In Progress)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/forgiveness-in-progress/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/forgiveness-in-progress/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking a lot about it, this idea, forgiveness. That might be all I have on it right now, which raises a meta question for the blog - is that enough to publish?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To which I&amp;rsquo;d ask myself - what&amp;rsquo;s the point of the blog? Is it mostly for others? Or mostly for me?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And then I&amp;rsquo;d of course realize, as I am, that the same question can be asked about forgiveness itself.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More on Ursula K. Le Guin</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/more-on-ursula-k-le-guin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/more-on-ursula-k-le-guin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Reading more of her this morning and I don&amp;rsquo;t want to stop. There is a joy in her words, an aliveness, that is contagious. I feel as though she does not want to stop writing, and thus, perhaps, I don&amp;rsquo;t want to stop reading.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The topics vary wildly from why armed forces wear uniforms to the paucity of &amp;lsquo;growth&amp;rsquo; as the prevailing metaphor for our entire way of being and doing. No matter the details though, I want to keep reading.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ursula K. Le Guin Appreciation Post</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/ursula-k-le-guin-appreciation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/ursula-k-le-guin-appreciation/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m reading her book right now, No Time To Spare, and am filled with this familiar feeling of how it feels when you&amp;rsquo;re reading someone and just feel&amp;hellip;seen. Understood, yes, but more than that, like your own way of understanding itself is being reflected back to you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Or, in other words, she&amp;rsquo;s just smart and I like how her brain moves ideas around, how it thinks and how she shares that thinking with the world.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
