<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Reading on Both Are True</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/reading/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Reading on Both Are True</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.150.1</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/reading/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>positioning</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/positioning/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/positioning/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>true commitment to the bit</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/true-commitment-to-the-bit/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/true-commitment-to-the-bit/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;![Pasted image 20251017213150.png](/images/Pasted image 20251017213150.png)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Soooo this actor and writer Richard Ayoade wrote a book called The Unfinished Harauld Hughes which is about a writer of books and screenplays and other things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And as part of writing that book, Ayoade also wrote and published actual books by his fictional character Harauld Hughes!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;rsquo;s Wallace Shawn explaining what Ayoade did:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;_many writers have invented characters who are writers—but do you know any other writer who has not only invented a character who is a writer but who has then gone on to actually write and publish that imaginary writer’s complete works? Richard Ayoade has done that, and if you take out your Kindle and look up Harauld Hughes, Faber will be glad to send you Hughes’s collected plays, poems, prose pieces, and screenplays, all in fact written by Richard Ayoade.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More on Ursula K. Le Guin</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/more-on-ursula-k-le-guin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/more-on-ursula-k-le-guin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Reading more of her this morning and I don&amp;rsquo;t want to stop. There is a joy in her words, an aliveness, that is contagious. I feel as though she does not want to stop writing, and thus, perhaps, I don&amp;rsquo;t want to stop reading.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The topics vary wildly from why armed forces wear uniforms to the paucity of &amp;lsquo;growth&amp;rsquo; as the prevailing metaphor for our entire way of being and doing. No matter the details though, I want to keep reading.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ursula K. Le Guin Appreciation Post</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/ursula-k-le-guin-appreciation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/ursula-k-le-guin-appreciation/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m reading her book right now, No Time To Spare, and am filled with this familiar feeling of how it feels when you&amp;rsquo;re reading someone and just feel&amp;hellip;seen. Understood, yes, but more than that, like your own way of understanding itself is being reflected back to you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Or, in other words, she&amp;rsquo;s just smart and I like how her brain moves ideas around, how it thinks and how she shares that thinking with the world.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
